nice to meet you.
初めまして
This is Kitajima, the president.
社長の北島です
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Rikao-chan is so cute.
りかおちゃんめっちゃ可愛いじゃん
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃったよ
19 years old.
19歳
yes.
はい
Thanks, I don't think I know why you're taking pictures, but
ありがとちょっとなんで撮ってるか分からないと思うんだけど、
Well, just in case, I look like this,
まあ一応ね、僕こんな見た目だから、
So that you won't be told later that something was dropped,
あとでなんか落とされましたとか言われないために、
I'm taking some photos, but I think my mom did the interview.
一応撮ってるんだけど、 うちのママが面接したと思うんだけど、
Things that I didn't hear during the interview, things that I wasn't told, etc.
面接時に聞いてなかった話とか、 これ言われてないよとか、
What I'm going to say now, so that you don't have to pour water on it later.
今から言う話とか、後で水かけるようにならないために、
I'm just taking some pictures for record purposes.
ちょっと記録用として撮ってるから、
I guess it's okay if you just accept that.
それだけ了承いただけたら大丈夫かな
If Rika-chan doesn't say this later, I'll do it two more times.
後でりかちゃんもこれ言われてないよとなったら後2回するから
Hey, this video.
ね、 この動画
I would like to introduce you to Osaki.
一応紹介しとくね、じゅう、大崎
This is Osaki.
大崎です
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Yoshinari was introduced to me.
吉成は紹介してもらったね
I agree.
そうですね
Well, I'll explain.
ね、説明やります
With mom.
ママと一緒にね
Well, I'll give you some additional explanation now.
じゃあちょっと、今から追加説明します
You were painting your body today, right?
今日体系塗ってたよね?
I agree.
そうですね
why?
なぜ?
It's already going well.
もうよく入ってるな
It's already 40% today.
もう今日4割
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
Good for you, Rika-chan.
よかったね、りかちゃん
You can make a lot of money.
めっちゃ稼げるよ
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
Really.
本当に
The body painting will be done in about an hour and a half.
体系塗りがあと1時間半後か
that's right.
そう です
So let me explain the colors a little bit.
じゃあちょっと色を説明していくんでね
I'm beautiful too.
私も綺麗だね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You have a boyfriend, right?
彼氏いるよね?
I'm not there.
いないです
Are you not there?
いないの?
yes.
はい
Eh, what about a sex friend?
え、セフレは?
There aren't any.
いないですよ
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
yes.
はい
He's very serious.
めっちゃ真面目じゃん
How much experience do you have?
経験率何くらい?
There are about 5 people.
5人くらいです
About 5 people?
5人くらい?
yes.
はい
Then you don't know anything.
じゃあ 何も分かってないね
I don't understand.
分かんないです
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
When was the last time you had sex?
最後いつエッチしたの?
About a month ago.
1ヶ月くらい前に
You know that.
それは知ってるじゃん
With whom?
誰としたん?
Oh, it's just an app.
え、ちょっとアプリの
App?
アプリ?
yes.
はい
5th person on the app?
アプリで5人目?
yes.
はい
Why did you do that?
なんでそんなやっちゃったの?
I feel lonely.
寂しくて
Were you lonely?
寂しかった?
yes.
はい
I'll be fine with this job now.
もうこの仕事したら大丈夫だよ
Loneliness too.
寂しさもね
You can get away with it, and you can make money too.
な げられるし、お金も稼げるし
That's right.
そうなんだよ
Well, by the way, all the girls who have never worked at our shop before.
まあそれはそうとね、うちのお店未経験の女の子全員ね、
It's called a practical training course, where the staff actually teaches you what kind of work they do.
実技講習といって、スタッフが実際にどんな仕事内容とか教えて、
I'll tell you what the job entails, but
仕事内容こんなんだよと教えてくんだけど、
If I don't accept that, I won't get the job.
それ受けないと仕事受けないんだけど、
Is that okay?
それ大丈夫かな?
No, I haven't heard of that.
いや、ちょっとそれは聞いてないです
That's why I'm explaining it now.
だから今説明してるんだけどね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Can you negotiate?
交渉受けれる?
ah.
ああ
If you don't answer properly, it won't be okay if it turns out to be rape.
ちゃんと答えてくれないと、レイプになったらダメだから
I can go.
いけます
Can you go?
いける?
yes.
はい
I see.
そっか
Well, let's have fun negotiating.
ま、せっかくは楽しく交渉しようよ
yes.
はい
hey.
ね
How many cups is this?
これ何カップなの?
this.
これ
It's D.
Dです
D cup?
Dカップ?
yes.
はい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Well, I have to make sure to check for bulges.
まあね、ぶだげのチェックとかしっかりしなきゃいけない
yes.
はい
hey.
ね
Because Kozaki is doing it.
小崎がやってるからね
yes.
はい
Then let me negotiate.
じゃあ俺、交渉してやれ
Shall we go together?
一 緒に行こうか
yes.
はい
It also includes New Ike after this.
この後のニューアイクも入ってるからね
yes.
はい
It's no good unless you do a little new check.
ちょっとニューアイクチェックとかもしないとダメだじゃん
Yeah.
うん
If this were the case, customers would be in trouble.
こんな状態だったらお客さん困っちゃうからね
yes.
はい
Are you really okay?
本当に大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Oh my god.
いや、なんてなんて
It's true.
本当だよ
What?
なんて?
Are you negotiating?
交渉ですか?
Yes, negotiation.
うん、交渉
this?
これ?
yes.
はい
It's a negotiation.
交渉だよ
why?
なんで?
I have to check my body properly.
ちゃんと体のチェックしなきゃ
I feel like that.
そうな気もする
Yeah.
うん
That's no good.
そこはダメです
Why?
なんでだろう?
why?
なんで?
Hey, why?
ね え、なんで?
fantasy.
ファンタジー
Yeah.
うん
He had a cute posture.
かわいい姿勢つけてた
That's amazing, can I be tingly?
すごいね、ツンツンしていい?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Hey, can I have a little fun with you?
ねえ、ちょっとツンツンしていい?
yes.
はい
What?
え、なんだ?
Yes.
はいって
That's not negotiation, right?
それ交渉じゃないでしょ
Isn't this a negotiation?
これ、交渉じゃないですかね
Maybe it's time to check your body style.
ちゃんとちょっと体のスタイルチェックかいかもね
Just stand up for a moment.
一 回 ちょっと立ってごらん
Well then, just a moment.
じゃあ ちょっと
It's cute.
かわいいね
Bring out the bell.
ベルを出してごらん
Bae.
ベーって
Even more disgusting.
もっと嫌らしく
Now you can lick my dick.
これでおちんちん舐めるんだね
Hey.
ねえ
It's cute.
かわいいね
Let's check the bell for a moment.
ちょっとベルのチェックしようか
Let's check out Bell.
ベルのチェックしよう
What do you think?
どうなの?
Rika-chan.
りかちゃん
Did you check the bell?
ベルのチェックできた?
I think it was done.
できたと思います
Oh, you made it?
え、できたの?
Hey, come on.
ちょ、おいで
He's very proactive.
すごい積極的じゃん
Well, I guess so.
えー、そうですかね
Well then, let's check it out.
じゃあおしんチェックしようか
Hey, let me check your style.
ねえ、ちょっとスタイルチェックするよ
First, move away a little.
まずちょっと離れて
Just once, yes, once around.
一回ちょっと、はい、一周して
Yes, turn around.
はい、後ろ向いて
So let's try the fourth one next time.
じゃあ次ちょっと4つ目になってみようか
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
This is why style checking is so important.
これがスタイルチェック大事なことだからね
I have to tell the customer what kind of butt it is.
お客さんにほら、どんなお尻かって伝えなきゃいけないから
Yes, get on your butt and knees here.
はい、お尻ひざついてここ
Yeah, ride it.
うん、乗って
Yes, through your waist.
はい、腰を通して
Have a butt.
お尻つきやして
Pass through your waist.
腰を通して
fault.
あら
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It's really smooth.
めっちゃスブスブだね
skin.
肌
Oh, that's a nice ass.
あら、いいお尻じゃん
You're cutting your butt off to the customer.
お尻をお客さん切りしてますよね
What do you feel?
どういうのか感じるの?
Yeah.
うん
Is it like this?
こういう感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's do this forever.
じゃあずっとやってあげようか
We have to please our customers.
お客さんに喜ばせなきゃな
I want you to do it forever.
ずっとしてほしいですって
Yeah.
うん
It's a lecture.
講習だからね
I need you to say that properly.
ちゃんとそういうの言ってくれないと
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうするの?
I'm standing on my feet.
足パタパタ立ってるよ
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
ねえ
19 years old is the best.
19歳最高だね
Yeah.
うん
The customer will touch your pussy a lot like this.
お客さんこうやっておまんこいっぱい触ってくるからね
What can I do about pants?
パンツどうしたらできない
Sometimes you can get in.
入れられることもあるよ
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうする?
At times like that.
そういう時は
Yeah.
うん
You don't understand, right?
分からないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
That's why I'm going to teach you that.
だからそれを講習するからね
Are your pants damp?
なんかパンツ湿ってない?
Is it just my imagination?
気のせい?
The color is changing, isn't it?
色変わってきてますよね
This is changing color.
色変わってるよこれ
Hey.
ねえ
In a slightly darker part.
ちょっと濃い部分に
Huh?
あれ?
It seems like things are changing around here.
なんかこれ、ここら辺なんか色変わってるよ
River-chan.
りばちゃん
Is it because of my imagination?
気 のせい?
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいなの?
Yeah.
うん
It's not just my imagination.
気のせいじゃないよね
Yeah.
うん
Definitely this.
絶 対これ
Yeah.
うん
That's dangerous.
やばいじゃん
Let's check out your breasts for a moment.
ちょっと感じのおっぱいチェックいこうか
yes.
はい
Come on, look.
おいで、ほら
This is really big.
めっちゃでかいよこれ
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's powerful.
迫力があるよ
is that so.
そうですか
You may not have noticed, but did you notice that I was taking Sylhet?
気づいてないかもしれないけど、シレット取ってるの気づいてた?
Yeah.
うん
If I didn't go to work properly,
これ、ちゃんと出勤しなかったら、
I'll show it to your mom.
お母さんに見せるからね
Yeah.
ええ
good?
いい?
Please don't do that.
それはやめてください
Yeah.
うん
Do you go to work properly?
ちゃんと出勤する?
yes.
はい
We really do it.
俺ら本当にやるからね
yes.
はい
Don't let that happen.
そんなさせないでね
Have fun.
楽しく
Let's make it a memory.
思い出のはめどりにしよう
Yeah.
うん
It's just a reward.
報酬だからね、ただ
yes.
はい
Do you have a D cup?
Dカップある?
Can't you tell on clothes?
服の上じゃわかんないかな?
Yeah.
うん
I can't tell if you're wearing clothes, so let's take them off for a bit.
服の上じゃわかんないから、ちょっと脱ごうか
Hey.
ねえ
yes.
はい
How do I take it off?
どうやって脱ぐの?
this.
これ
It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
ねえ
Well then, let's check your armpit hair.
じゃあ ちょっとね、脇毛のチェックしようか
yes.
はい
Armpit hair armpit hair.
脇毛脇毛です
If there is any unshaved hair, push it out.
剃り残しあったら、押し抜きだよ
Got it?
分かった?
yes.
はい
Yuppon, isn't it growing?
ゆっぽん、生えてるんじゃない?
this.
これ
When did you shave?
いつ剃ったの?
Oh, yesterday.
え、昨日
Did you shave yesterday?
昨日剃った?
Yeah.
うん
Just kidding.
冗談だよ
Yeah.
ええ
Yes, I disagree.
はい、反対
Oh, it's not growing.
ああ、生えてないじゃん
Yeah.
うん
If I had grown one, it would have been a punishment game.
一本ぐらい生やしてたら、罰ゲームだったけどね
You wanted to take the punishment game, right?
罰ゲーム受けたかったでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
I see, no.
なるほど、ない
picture?
え?
What?
なんて?
Who is it?
誰です?
Who would it be?
誰でしょう?
It's kind of a noisy mouth.
なんか、うるさい口だね
Yes, I want to kiss you.
はい、キスしとくな
yes.
はい
With small blooms.
小咲きと
Yes, just for 5 minutes while kissing.
はい、キスしながら5分だけで
Yes, I'm going to put out more spells.
はい、もっとペル出しとくなって
Oh yeah, should I remove the brush?
そうそう、ブラシ外すか
Let's check various things
チクビ色々確認しよっ
mosquito.
か
You can tell if you're looking at this by what color it is.
これ、 何色かでご覧にしてるか分かるからね
You're touching your right chin a lot, aren't you?
結構右のチクビ触ってるでしょ?
Yeah.
ええ
Hey, what's going on?
ねえ、どうなの?
Just say it.
言ってごらん
It may be reflected.
映ってるかもしれない
When did you see it?
いつご覧にした?
最後
You have really nice breasts.
めっちゃいいおっぱいしてるじゃん
Yeah.
ええ
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
That's nice.
いいねえ
How old is your mother?
お母さん何歳?
I'm 48 years old.
48歳です
48 years old?
48歳?
Please bring me for a moment.
ちょっと連れてきておいで
No.
ダメです
No?
ダメ?
why?
なんで?
I'm running an introduction campaign.
紹介キャンペやってるよ
No.
ダメです
If you introduce me to your mother, I'll give you five cards like this.
お母さん紹介してくれたら、こうカード5枚あげるよ
I'll give you a lesson, Mom.
俺が講習してあげるから、お母さん
No.
ダメです
No?
ダメ?
No way.
ダメな
Can you touch me from behind?
後ろからチクビ触ってもらえ?
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
Shall I touch it?
俺が触ろうか
Shall I try taking my underwear off?
下脱がしてみようか
Shall I check your pussy?
マンコチェックしようか
copper?
どう?
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Maybe.
かもしれない
Which one?
どっち?
I have to say it properly.
ちゃんと言わなきゃ
It's no good if your mother makes a prediction, right?
お母さんの予想するとダメでしょ?
I got a little wet.
ちょっと濡れました
picture?
え?
I got wet.
濡れました
Did you get wet?
濡れちゃった?
Shall I check the pants as well?
パンツも同じチェックしようか
Hey, what's going on with this?
ねえ、これどうなってんのかな?
Hey, this.
ねえ、これ
Properly.
ちゃんと
Huh?
あれ?
What can I say about this?
何を言いましょう、これ
I got wet.
濡れました
What is this?
これ何これ?
何これ?
What is this?
これ何これ?
Hey, what is this?
ねえ、これ何なの?
What is this?
何これ?
what?
何?
What is this?
何これ?
Shall I send this to my mom?
お母さんに送ろうか、これ
No.
ダメです
Hey.
ねえ
Mom said she got wet.
お母さん濡れましたって
Don't like it?
嫌?
Look at it in an M-shape.
ちょっとM字になってごらん
Oh, let's check this out.
あ、マンクチェックしよう、これ
I'm a pie fan.
パイファンじゃん
When did you take the photo?
いつ撮ったの?
Ototsu.
おとつ
Did you take a picture of Ototsu?
おとつ撮ったの?
Ah, yes.
あ、 そう
Legs, do this yourself.
足をね、自分でこう
I'll take a photo like this.
こう写真撮ってあげるからね
I'll make a photo of the panel.
パネル写真にしてあげる
Yes, pace.
はい、ペースして
I took this photo for a customer.
お客さん用に撮ったからね
But here.
ここ だけど
Let's make it look good here.
いい形にしますね、ここ
Aren't these littles big?
これ、リトルス大きくない?
Will it get bigger?
大きくなっちゃうんですか?
It's going to get bigger though.
大きくなっちゃうんですけどね
What if I hit the rotor?
ローター当てたらどうなの?
heavy.
重い
Can you guess the weight?
重さとか当てる?
It might be a little strong.
少し強いかもしれない
strong?
強い?
yes.
はい
Does that mean it's good?
それは良いってこと?
Does that mean it's bad?
悪いってこと?
Yeah, I don't know.
うん、分かんない
Shall we go now?
すぐ行っちゃう?
I think I'll go.
行っちゃうと思う
Do you think I'll go?
行っちゃうと思う?
Let's give it a try.
ちょっと試してみましょうか
Shall we try Osaki's fingers first?
まず、大崎の指から試してみる?
Yeah.
うん
Or do you want to try toys first?
それとも、おもちゃから試したい?
Yeah.
うん
Good job, Rin.
よいしょ、りん
yes.
はい
Well, then.
では、まっ
Let's take a guess.
さあ、当ててみようか
hey.
ね
I didn't guess what you said earlier, but is it already going to be this pink?
さっき当てて言ったわけでも、もうこんなピンカになるんですか?
Yeah.
うん
I'll give you 15 minutes.
15分も当てるよ
Yeah.
うん
Hey, are you okay?
ねえ、大丈夫?
I haven't guessed it properly yet.
まだ、ちゃんと当ててないよ
Properly?
ちゃんと?
Yeah.
うん
Because I spread it out.
広げたから
The back can hold up too.
後ろも耐えれて
I have to tell you, look, please guess.
ちゃんと、ほら、当ててくださいって言わなきゃ
If you do Osaki, you'll have sex with me next time.
大崎やったら、次俺とエッチするからね
Got it?
分かった?
yes.
はい
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
I was just joking.
冗談で言ったんだけど
Is it okay?
いいの?
No.
ダメです
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
Well, give me another 15 minutes.
じゃあ、もう15分当ててください
I guess I'm guessing something suspicious.
なんか、 なんか怪しいの当ててるよ、
this.
これ
what?
何?
this.
これ
picture?
え?
Will the tide blow?
潮とか吹いちゃう?
Are you going to blow it?
吹いちゃうんだよ?
Maybe.
もしかして
It's like, Okay.
よーさいな、みたいな
yes.
はい
Did you stretch your legs?
足伸ばしたかな?
Isn't this easier to get to?
この方が行きやすいでしょ?
Shall we go?
行っちゃいます?
Yeah.
うん
Shall we go?
行っちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Kosaki, I'll guess.
小崎、俺、当ててやるわ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Still not going?
まだ行かない?
picture?
え?
I have to say I'm going because I'm going properly.
ちゃんと行くから行くって言わなきゃ
It won't end?
終わんないよ?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Can't you hear me?
聞こえない?
I'm going out.
出まいちゃう
picture?
え?
I'm leaving.
出 まいちゃう
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
terrible?
やばい?
Yeah.
うん
I haven't taken care of it.
手 当ててないよ
You've already guessed it yourself.
自分でもう当ててるじゃん
what happened?
どうしたの?
Do you want me to guess?
当ててほしいの?
picture?
え?
Still not satisfied?
まだ満足しないの?
I have a strong desire to do something.
ちょっとする気が強くて
how was it?
どうだった?
Some customers will guess for an hour.
お客さんによって1時間当ててくる人がいるよ
picture?
え?
yes.
はい
At times like that, I have to go over and say it's no good.
そういう時は何回も行って、ダメですって言うなきゃ
Shall we check it out wet?
濡れてチェックしようか
This is so wet.
なんかビチョビチョだよ、これ
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
No.
ダメだよ
It's soaking wet.
ビチョビチョだよ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Yeah.
うん
I won't be able to defend myself forever even if I attack a peep.
のぞきの攻めも一人して、いつまでも守らないよ
Take a peek, it's about time you put it in your finger.
のぞき、そろそろ指に入れてやったら
It would be easier if you came a little closer to me.
もうちょっと手前に来てもらった方がやりやすいね
You better come over here to the front.
こっち、前の方に来たほうがいい
Ho
ほ
and others.
ら
Yeah.
うん
It has been hosted.
司 会されてきましたね
Will you be hosting?
司会されるの?
You're amazing, Mom.
すごいお前、お母さん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah, that's fine.
うん、いいです
Are you good at blowjobs?
フェラとか得意?
Yeah.
うん
How old were you when you had your first blowjob?
初めてフェラしたら何歳だ?
17 years old.
17歳
17 years old?
17歳?
I was 17 years old when I had my first experience?
初体験も17歳?
That's right.
そうなんです
Is that person dating?
その人は付き合ってるかな?
that's right.
そうです
Is that so?
そうなの?
Is that person not in contact with you now?
その人は今連絡取ってないの?
Yeah, I haven't taken it.
うん、取ってないです
Haven't you taken it yet?
取 ってない?
Do you want to meet that person again?
その人にもう一回会いたい?
How was your first day?
初めての日どうだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Were you given a cleaning blow job?
お掃除フェラとかさせられた?
I've done it before.
したことある
Have you ever done that?
したことある?
No?
ダメ?
No.
ダメだよ
yes.
はい
I can ride it really well.
めっちゃ乗れてるやん
Shall I give you a blowjob?
フェラさせようか
Osaki I haven't taken a bath.
大崎お風呂入ってないからね
It might smell a bit like dick.
ちょっとおチンコ臭いかもしれない
Let's take a little sniff.
ちょっとクンクン嗅いでみようか
yes.
はい
Squat down.
しゃがんで
Why don't you just smell Osaki's dick?
ちょっと大崎のおチンコ、クンクン嗅いでごらん?
First, check the smell.
まず匂いチェックだよ
copper?
どう?
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you like that?
そういうの好きなの?
Hey.
ねえ
What is the size of this dick out of the five men of all time?
歴代5人の中でこのチンコ何番目の大きさ?
This is the 6th person, right?
これ6人目だよね?
None out of 6 people?
6人中ない?
this.
これ
I don't know.
わかんない
Say it properly.
ちゃんと言って
About 3rd place.
3位くらい
No way, that's how you say it.
ダメだよ、その言い方しちゃう
I have to say it's number 1.
1位って言わなきゃ
It's a lecture.
講習だよ
The customer gets disappointed when I say that my dick is number 3.
お客さん、チンコ3位って言ったらお客さんがガッカイしちゃう
Yo.
よ
1st place.
1位 です
What's in first place?
どこがどう1位なの?
It's my favorite shape.
私にとって好きな形ですって
私にとって好きな形です
I have to say it properly.
ちゃんと言わなきゃ
If you say you're in 3rd place, it's a punishment.
3位って言ったらお仕置きだな
I don't usually do actual training, but I will.
いつも本番講習しないけど、本番するからね
This is your punishment, you understand?
お仕置きだよ、分かった?
Let me lick it properly.
ちゃんと舐めてもらおう
You might be feeling angry.
腹当たっちゃってるかもしれないですね
Are you hungry?
腹当たっちゃってる?
Let me open my mouth wide.
大きく口開けてもらおう
What about now?
今はどうなの?
He's really good at it.
めっちゃ上手です
good?
上手?
Would you like me to lick you a little later?
ちょっと後で俺も舐めてもらおうか
Licca-chan, look at me and make a peace.
リカちゃん、こっち見てピースして
Lick while peace.
ピースしながら舐めて
Shall I send a video message to my mom?
お母さんにビデオメッセージを送ろうか
A video message from a 19-year-old.
19歳のビデオメッセージ
I can now lick your cock.
おチンポ舐められるようになりました
Just say that.
って 言ってごらん
While speaking.
声ながら
Yes, say it.
はい、言ってごらん
I don't understand what you're saying.
何言ってるか分かんないわ
What's your name?
おましょこがあんの?
I've never done this before.
したことないですよ、これ
You shot it in a nice way.
いい感じに撮ってんじゃん
Come sit next to me and lick me.
ちょっとおそばになりながら舐めてごらん
Try licking it while sitting next to it.
おそばになりながら舐めてごらん
Did I not check your butt?
お尻をチェックしてなくてしたっけ?
I haven't.
してないね
Is this area easy to feel?
この辺が感じやすいの?
Where do you feel the most?
どこが感じやすいの?
child
こ
Drop it properly.
っち 落として、ちゃんと
I have to do it properly.
ちゃんとやらなきゃ
Hey.
ねえ
Can I call you?
電話てよっか?
Do it properly?
ちゃんとしてよ?
Got it?
分かった?
Hey.
ねえ
Let's put it in, Wasagi.
入れちゃおうか、わさぎ
Leah, look at me.
リアちゃん、こっちを見て
Did you know that it's going to be a real performance?
本番するから分かった?
I'm going to put my cock in you raw.
生でおチンチン入れるよ
Hey, I'm going to put your cock in you raw.
ねえ、生でおチンチン入れるよ
Let me tell you about the situation when you get a new name.
新名取る状況教えてやろうか
She's a weak woman.
押しに弱い女だよ
Just tell me that I'm not very pushy.
私、押しに弱いですって言ってほら
What's your weakness?
何が弱いの?
Me eating chicken.
チキンをチンする俺
You can't make a sound.
声出てねえじゃん
Rika-chan, it's good to be friends.
リカちゃん、仲良しにいいんだよね
Is it good for good friends?
仲良しにいいの?
Which one?
どっち?
picture?
え?
What kind of weak woman?
何の弱い女だって?
I'm also a good girl to get along with.
私、仲良しにいい女だって
Please take it out inside.
中で出してください
What happened to the straw rabbit?
わらわさぎ、どうした?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's getting really weak.
すごい弱くなってきた
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Rika-chan, please kneel properly.
リカちゃん、ちゃんと膝のしていいよ
Look further up.
もっと上にほら
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
So let's have a hard time.
それでガンガンついてもらおう
Is it possible?
いけそうなのか?
That's enough.
もういいよ
Let me take it out.
出してもらおう
I feel like it's okay now.
もういい気がする
もういい気がするよ
It's still okay.
まだ大丈夫だよ
Come on, I'll keep it in for a long time.
お さき、まだずっと入れるから
Okay?
いいよっか
Yes, please teach me.
はい、教え付け出して
There will be two issues in a row.
2連発行くからね
There are accidents like this too.
こういう事故もあるから
The staff.
スタッフはね
I'll follow you hard, Osaki.
ガンガンついてやる、おさき
Rika-chan, you're not satisfied.
リカちゃん、満足してないよね
It's like this.
こんなんじゃ
Hey, go ahead.
ほら、行ってごらん
Daddy, mommy, daddy
パパ、ママ、パパ、
Daddy.
パ パ
It's my first time.
初めてやから
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
yes.
はい
Could you please follow me more?
もっとついてもらえたか?
Have you ever done anything?
事情やったことある?
Well, something has been done.
あれ、何かできてるじゃん
what?
何 ですか?
Who taught you this?
誰に教えてもらったの?
How old is my person?
私の人、何歳?
18 years old.
18歳
partner?
相手?
At 18 years old, it's a shame.
18歳にして、なせがきだな
Very.
非常に
It becomes an M-shape.
M字になってね
Put your feet up and do some paco-paco.
足立てて、パコパコしてね
Osaki, does it hurt?
おさき、痛い?
It hurts so bad.
めちゃめちゃ痛い
Is it okay if I cum inside?
中に出しちゃっても大丈夫?
Also.
また
Mama can do this.
これ、ママちゃんできちゃうね
This is out.
出ちゃったね、これ
You were ejaculated twice.
2回、中出されたね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's okay if you wash it.
洗えば大丈夫だよ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's okay if you wash it.
洗えば大丈夫だから
Got it?
分かった?
yes.
はい
Stand up, stand up.
立って立って
Let's do some cleaning blowjob.
お掃除フェラーしようか
Have you ever cleaned a room at home?
家のお部屋の掃除したことある?
there is.
あります
Because I'm with you too.
俺も一緒だから
I'll clean up later.
あと片付けだからね
Osaki was in front of me.
おさきが前の目だった
You did it properly.
ちゃんとできたじゃん
Yes, please sit down.
はい、座ってください
how was it?
どうだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
気持ちよかったじゃん
Because I learned a lot.
ちゃんと勉強になったから
I learned a lot.
勉強になりました
Finally, M-shaped Naoka.
最後、M字なおうか
Look at the letter M.
M字なってごらん
It was served inside.
中に出されました
Please nominate.
指名してください
Okay, I have time to get the trial version.
よし、体験入手のお時間あるから、
Shall I take a shower and get ready?
シャワー浴びて準備しようか
yes.
はい
Take a shower.
シャワー浴びて